BENEDYKT CIEŚLIŃSKI

GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER

Website: benedyktcieslinski.com

Email: benedykt.cieslinski@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a professional gameplay programmer with a BA (Hons) in Game Development and industry experience. I have successfully collaborated with multidisciplinary teams which include artists, audio engineers, designers, and animators, on various game projects. My experience includes working with Unity, C#, and ECS, as well as using Jira, Confluence, and Perforce/Git for version control. Furthermore, I have used the Agile workflow with the scrum structure and often had to be flexible in my role to help out the team in many ways. I am always keen on learning new things and work in teams to deliver new and fun mechanics.

PROGRAMMING

INDUSTRY SKILL

.Net programming UE Blueprints Agile Workflow C# C++ Git/Perforce

Visual Studio/Rider Jira/Liquid planner

CSS HTML Confluence

ENGINES

LANGUAGES

Unity Engine Unreal Engine Polish - Native English - Fluent

EDUCATION

BA(Hons) Game Development: Programming

2020 - 2023

Falmouth University, England

With a main focus on mimicking industry development process when creating video games, I created games in teams with a big focus on collaboration. Utilizing Agile and version control using Git.

EXPERIENCE

Robocraft 2

2023 - 2024

Unity, ECS/DOTS | Freejam

Using Svelto ECS, I collaborated closely with designers, artists, and backend teams to deliver polished gameplay features. My work included but is not limited to creating a scoreboard, crosshairs based on player weapons, gamepad support, and a system to convert game objects into entities. I also developed a currency exchange for buying and selling blocks. During my work I extensively used Jira/Liquid planner, Confluence and Perforce for version control.

Survival Of The Cutest

2022-2023

<u>Unreal Engine 5.1, Blueprints | University project</u>

As part of a 12 person team I have implemented functional UI in the form on main menus and player HUD. I also developed the player movement and camera controller, including camera shake. In addition to that I have designed and implemented all AI characters using behaviour trees. I also helped implement animations and audio into the project.

Lost Lab

2022

Unity, C# | University project

Recreated a scanner mechanic able of displaying up to 80 million points using C# and VFX Graph. Added the ability to customize individual points by using a custom struct to hold data of each point and a graphics buffer to send that data to the shader. This project required me to quickly adapt and learn new tools.